[
	{
		"question": "noticeable",
		"answer": "conspicuous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "need",
		"answer": "require",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rebuke",
		"answer": "fault",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "proud",
		"answer": "conceited",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "adversary",
		"answer": "opponent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "alliance",
		"answer": "union",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "enraged",
		"answer": "incensed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "grimace",
		"answer": "frown",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "peculiar",
		"answer": "strange",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "foreseen",
		"answer": "expected",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fixed",
		"answer": "static",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hazardous",
		"answer": "dangerous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "endless",
		"answer": "infinite",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mediocre",
		"answer": "average",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "proposal",
		"answer": "suggestion",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "chief",
		"answer": "principal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "stiff",
		"answer": "rigid",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "inept",
		"answer": "useless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shy",
		"answer": "bashful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "cease",
		"answer": "terminate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "buys",
		"answer": "purchases",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "assist",
		"answer": "support",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "toiled",
		"answer": "worked",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "tedious",
		"answer": "boring",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "positive",
		"answer": "optimistic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "occurring",
		"answer": "happening",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "revolves",
		"answer": "rotates",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "embellish",
		"answer": "decorate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "substantial",
		"answer": "considerable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dangerous",
		"answer": "hazardous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hard",
		"answer": "difficult",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "eccentric",
		"answer": "peculiar",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "consider",
		"answer": "contemplate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "visitor",
		"answer": "guest",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "majestic",
		"answer": "regal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "funny",
		"answer": "humorous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "energetic",
		"answer": "vigorous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "separate",
		"answer": "unconnected",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "water",
		"answer": "hydrate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "appreciate",
		"answer": "value",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "monarchy",
		"answer": "royalty",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "anger",
		"answer": "wrath",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "recommend",
		"answer": "suggest",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "scorched",
		"answer": "charred",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "plan",
		"answer": "scheme",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "quaking",
		"answer": "trembling",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "impertinent",
		"answer": "rude",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wrong",
		"answer": "incorrect",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "abode",
		"answer": "home",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "friendly",
		"answer": "amiable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "coarse",
		"answer": "rough",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "gigantic",
		"answer": "colossal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "melancholy",
		"answer": "sadness",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "trivial",
		"answer": "unimportant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "diminish",
		"answer": "decrease",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "avidly",
		"answer": "eagerly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "agree",
		"answer": "concur",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "internal",
		"answer": "interior",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "finish",
		"answer": "conclude",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "loathe",
		"answer": "despise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rubbish",
		"answer": "nonsense",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rapidly",
		"answer": "quickly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unenthusiastic",
		"answer": "apathetic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mad",
		"answer": "insane",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "strong",
		"answer": "durable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "powerful",
		"answer": "potent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dusk",
		"answer": "twilight",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "still",
		"answer": "motionless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "civil",
		"answer": "polite",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "workmates",
		"answer": "colleagues",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "front",
		"answer": "anterior",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disregarding",
		"answer": "ignoring",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "deceased",
		"answer": "dead",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disclose",
		"answer": "reveal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "find",
		"answer": "discover",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "concept",
		"answer": "idea",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "job",
		"answer": "occupation",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "collided",
		"answer": "crashed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "careful",
		"answer": "cautious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hunger",
		"answer": "starvation",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "convinced",
		"answer": "certain",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "break",
		"answer": "damage",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "prior",
		"answer": "earlier",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "suitable",
		"answer": "appropriate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "normal",
		"answer": "ordinary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "reject",
		"answer": "veto",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dashed",
		"answer": "sprinted",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "area",
		"answer": "region",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "appropriate",
		"answer": "suitable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "outside",
		"answer": "exterior",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "overjoyed",
		"answer": "ecstatic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "furious",
		"answer": "livid",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "scold",
		"answer": "chide",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "glittering",
		"answer": "sparkling",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "talkative",
		"answer": "communicative",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "steady",
		"answer": "consistent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "drastic",
		"answer": "extreme",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rot",
		"answer": "decay",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "commerce",
		"answer": "business",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "expose",
		"answer": "uncover",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "persuade",
		"answer": "coax",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shaking",
		"answer": "quivering",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hectic",
		"answer": "busy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "winner",
		"answer": "victor",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hunt",
		"answer": "search",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "obstinate",
		"answer": "stubborn",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "daring",
		"answer": "audacious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "accomplish",
		"answer": "achieve",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ability",
		"answer": "aptitude",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "formerly",
		"answer": "previously",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "self-assured",
		"answer": "confident",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "magnify",
		"answer": "enlarge",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "calm",
		"answer": "tranquil",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "authentic",
		"answer": "real",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ghastly",
		"answer": "awful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wary",
		"answer": "reticent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "jealous",
		"answer": "envious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "burden",
		"answer": "load",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shirk",
		"answer": "evade",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "far",
		"answer": "distant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "expand",
		"answer": "enlarge",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fascinate",
		"answer": "engross",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "flaw",
		"answer": "imperfection",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "portion",
		"answer": "segment",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "roared",
		"answer": "bellowed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "discourteous",
		"answer": "impolite",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "chief",
		"answer": "leader",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lesser",
		"answer": "inferior",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ban",
		"answer": "prohibit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "steal",
		"answer": "plunder",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fabricate",
		"answer": "manufacture",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fracture",
		"answer": "break",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "storm",
		"answer": "tempest",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "naughty",
		"answer": "mischievous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "able",
		"answer": "competent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "complex",
		"answer": "difficult",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "chuckle",
		"answer": "giggle",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "revival",
		"answer": "restoration",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "insist",
		"answer": "assert",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "irritate",
		"answer": "annoy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "extra",
		"answer": "additional",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vanish",
		"answer": "disappear",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "anxious",
		"answer": "apprehensive",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "customary",
		"answer": "traditional",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "certain",
		"answer": "definite",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "meticulously",
		"answer": "carefully",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fake",
		"answer": "counterfeit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "durable",
		"answer": "enduring",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "commonplace",
		"answer": "ordinary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "odd",
		"answer": "peculiar",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dense",
		"answer": "thick",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "essential",
		"answer": "vital",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "easy",
		"answer": "effortless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hesitate",
		"answer": "pause",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "curt",
		"answer": "brusque",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "worried",
		"answer": "concerned",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dawn",
		"answer": "sunrise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unfriendly",
		"answer": "hostile",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fatal",
		"answer": "deadly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "industrious",
		"answer": "diligent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "smart",
		"answer": "intelligent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "brutal",
		"answer": "violent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "new",
		"answer": "novel",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "amble",
		"answer": "stroll",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "error",
		"answer": "mistake",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mumbled",
		"answer": "muttered",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "advantage",
		"answer": "benefit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "abnormal",
		"answer": "strange",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "story",
		"answer": "saga",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "chance",
		"answer": "opportunity",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "modern",
		"answer": "contemporary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "equivalent",
		"answer": "equal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "gratitude",
		"answer": "appreciation",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "admission",
		"answer": "confession",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "outcome",
		"answer": "result",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "chide",
		"answer": "reprimand",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "surroundings",
		"answer": "environment",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "union",
		"answer": "allegiance",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vicious",
		"answer": "violent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sullen",
		"answer": "morose",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "threatening",
		"answer": "menacing",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "raised",
		"answer": "elevated",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unimportant",
		"answer": "insignificant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ardent",
		"answer": "passionate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "upbeat",
		"answer": "cheerful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "consider",
		"answer": "contemplate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "opportunity",
		"answer": "chance",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sorry",
		"answer": "apologetic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "expect",
		"answer": "anticipate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "itch",
		"answer": "scratch",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "suspicious",
		"answer": "dubious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "choose",
		"answer": "select",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "boisterous",
		"answer": "energetic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "blameless",
		"answer": "innocent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fall",
		"answer": "collapse",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disorganised",
		"answer": "chaotic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mild",
		"answer": "moderate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "absent",
		"answer": "missing",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "comical",
		"answer": "funny",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "brisk",
		"answer": "quick",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "acute",
		"answer": "sharp",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "oblivious",
		"answer": "unaware",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "doubt",
		"answer": "mistrust",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "persuade",
		"answer": "cajole",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wander",
		"answer": "amble",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pungent",
		"answer": "smelly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "strange",
		"answer": "bizarre",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "satisfied",
		"answer": "content",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unexpected",
		"answer": "surprising",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "reluctant",
		"answer": "resistant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "constantly",
		"answer": "continually",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "animated",
		"answer": "lively",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "capture",
		"answer": "apprehend",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sad",
		"answer": "miserable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "keep",
		"answer": "retain",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "attach",
		"answer": "join",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "horrible",
		"answer": "hideous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rapidly",
		"answer": "speedily",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "untrustworthy",
		"answer": "dubious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "infamous",
		"answer": "notorious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "effort",
		"answer": "endeavour",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "perfume",
		"answer": "fragrance",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "secluded",
		"answer": "isolated",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "deserted",
		"answer": "abandoned",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "guilt",
		"answer": "remorse",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "eerie",
		"answer": "sinister",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "desert",
		"answer": "abandon",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "detach",
		"answer": "separate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sincerity",
		"answer": "honesty",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "make",
		"answer": "fabricate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "significant",
		"answer": "important",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mainly",
		"answer": "primarily",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "thaw",
		"answer": "melt",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "annually",
		"answer": "yearly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "complicated",
		"answer": "complex",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "argumentative",
		"answer": "defiant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "obscure",
		"answer": "unclear",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "raw",
		"answer": "uncooked",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pretty",
		"answer": "attractive",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "cruel",
		"answer": "harsh",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pointless",
		"answer": "futile",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dilemma",
		"answer": "problem",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "variation",
		"answer": "difference",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sad",
		"answer": "melancholy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "different",
		"answer": "diverse",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unhurried",
		"answer": "leisurely",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shortage",
		"answer": "scarcity",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pessimistic",
		"answer": "gloomy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "selects",
		"answer": "chooses",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "defend",
		"answer": "protect",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "aware",
		"answer": "conscious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unpleasant",
		"answer": "offensive",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "round",
		"answer": "circular",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "liberty",
		"answer": "freedom",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "huge",
		"answer": "immense",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "din",
		"answer": "commotion",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "impede",
		"answer": "hinder",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "taunt",
		"answer": "tease",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "silly",
		"answer": "absurd",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "enormous",
		"answer": "gigantic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "recover",
		"answer": "heal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "apex",
		"answer": "peak",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ordinary",
		"answer": "usual",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "emergency",
		"answer": "crisis",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "possible",
		"answer": "achievable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "chance",
		"answer": "opportunity",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "support",
		"answer": "recommend",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "exit",
		"answer": "leave",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "expensive",
		"answer": "costly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "nameless",
		"answer": "anonymous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "answer",
		"answer": "respond",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "commented",
		"answer": "remarked",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "change",
		"answer": "transform",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "display",
		"answer": "exhibit",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "car",
		"answer": "automobile",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "transfer",
		"answer": "reposition",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "necessary",
		"answer": "essential",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "brief",
		"answer": "short",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "persevered",
		"answer": "continued",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "substantial",
		"answer": "significant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "conflict",
		"answer": "disagreement",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "defy",
		"answer": "disobey",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "argument",
		"answer": "dispute",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "deceptive",
		"answer": "misleading",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "split",
		"answer": "divided",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "die",
		"answer": "perish",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fear",
		"answer": "trepidation",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "enclose",
		"answer": "contain",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "harmful",
		"answer": "detrimental",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fragile",
		"answer": "delicate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "bumpy",
		"answer": "turbulent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unlucky",
		"answer": "unfortunate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "compassion",
		"answer": "mercy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "perfect",
		"answer": "flawless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "explosive",
		"answer": "volatile",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "oblivious",
		"answer": "unaware",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pollute",
		"answer": "contaminate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "reliable",
		"answer": "dependable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "currently",
		"answer": "presently",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "jubilant",
		"answer": "delighted",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "arguable",
		"answer": "contentious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "aggravate",
		"answer": "irritate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "blunt",
		"answer": "abrupt",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "build",
		"answer": "construct",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "catch",
		"answer": "capture",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "haphazard",
		"answer": "random",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "greater",
		"answer": "superior",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "outside",
		"answer": "exterior",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lethargy",
		"answer": "weariness",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "converge",
		"answer": "meet",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "inept",
		"answer": "incompetent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "nice",
		"answer": "pleasant",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "many",
		"answer": "numerous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "ruin",
		"answer": "spoil",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disclose",
		"answer": "reveal",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pushed",
		"answer": "shoved",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "kind",
		"answer": "variety",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "house",
		"answer": "residence",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "instantly",
		"answer": "immediately",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "collect",
		"answer": "accumulate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "device",
		"answer": "machine",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "terrorise",
		"answer": "frighten",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "believable",
		"answer": "credible",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "prosper",
		"answer": "flourish",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "lack",
		"answer": "deficiency",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "danger",
		"answer": "peril",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hate",
		"answer": "loathe",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "eternal",
		"answer": "everlasting",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "keen",
		"answer": "enthusiastic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "location",
		"answer": "situation",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "adamant",
		"answer": "certain",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "terrain",
		"answer": "landscape",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "brave",
		"answer": "courageous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "back",
		"answer": "posterior",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "innocent",
		"answer": "blameless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "complete",
		"answer": "entire",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "illustrate",
		"answer": "depict",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "normal",
		"answer": "ordinary",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "cunning",
		"answer": "devious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hectic",
		"answer": "busy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hollow",
		"answer": "empty",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "sorrow",
		"answer": "woe",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "obvious",
		"answer": "apparent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "liveable",
		"answer": "habitable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "variety",
		"answer": "kind",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "rejoicing",
		"answer": "overjoyed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fluid",
		"answer": "liquid",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "puzzled",
		"answer": "perplexed",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "meticulous",
		"answer": "precise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "odour",
		"answer": "smell",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "confront",
		"answer": "face",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "hysterical",
		"answer": "frantic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "thrilled",
		"answer": "delighted",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "asked",
		"answer": "enquired",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "certain",
		"answer": "definite",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "category",
		"answer": "type",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "naughty",
		"answer": "mischievous",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "raucous",
		"answer": "rowdy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "harmful",
		"answer": "detrimental",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dearth",
		"answer": "scarcity",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "delicate",
		"answer": "fragile",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "keen",
		"answer": "eager",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mistake",
		"answer": "blunder",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "injure",
		"answer": "wound",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fault",
		"answer": "defect",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "enemy",
		"answer": "foe",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "trip",
		"answer": "journey",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "intentional",
		"answer": "deliberate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "likely",
		"answer": "probable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shamed",
		"answer": "disgraced",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "enhance",
		"answer": "improve",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vigilant",
		"answer": "watchful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shaking",
		"answer": "quivering",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "commotion",
		"answer": "disturbance",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "handy",
		"answer": "convenient",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "approach",
		"answer": "near",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "scared",
		"answer": "terrified",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wreck",
		"answer": "destroy",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "fascinating",
		"answer": "interesting",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "uniform",
		"answer": "consistent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "approximate",
		"answer": "estimate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "courageous",
		"answer": "heroic",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "stop",
		"answer": "cease",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "accumulate",
		"answer": "collect",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "pardon",
		"answer": "forgive",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "cloudy",
		"answer": "opaque",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "thin",
		"answer": "gaunt",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "external",
		"answer": "exterior",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "awful",
		"answer": "horrible",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mystify",
		"answer": "baffle",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "affable",
		"answer": "friendly",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "defer",
		"answer": "delay",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "moan",
		"answer": "complain",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "itemise",
		"answer": "catalogue",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "removable",
		"answer": "detachable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "vacant",
		"answer": "unoccupied",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "impolite",
		"answer": "insolent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "mend",
		"answer": "repair",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "modest",
		"answer": "humble",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "tiredness",
		"answer": "fatigue",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "obvious",
		"answer": "clear",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unified",
		"answer": "united",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "weak",
		"answer": "feeble",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "acknowledge",
		"answer": "recognise",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "covert",
		"answer": "secret",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "apparatus",
		"answer": "equipment",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disaster",
		"answer": "catastrophe",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "clever",
		"answer": "ingenious",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "answer",
		"answer": "respond",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "clear",
		"answer": "transparent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "intention",
		"answer": "objective",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "surplus",
		"answer": "extra",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "terrified",
		"answer": "petrified",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "restore",
		"answer": "renovate",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "new",
		"answer": "unused",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "auspicious",
		"answer": "promising",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "shy",
		"answer": "bashful",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "law",
		"answer": "rule",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "wrong",
		"answer": "incorrect",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "defeat",
		"answer": "vanquish",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "slim",
		"answer": "slender",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "agreeable",
		"answer": "enjoyable",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "unified",
		"answer": "united",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "abode",
		"answer": "home",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "chase",
		"answer": "pursue",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "alike",
		"answer": "similar",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "distinct",
		"answer": "clear",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "dry",
		"answer": "arid",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "prior",
		"answer": "preceding",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "apex",
		"answer": "peak",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "save",
		"answer": "rescue",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "aid",
		"answer": "assist",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "united",
		"answer": "unified",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "grand",
		"answer": "magnificent",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "occur",
		"answer": "happen",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "store",
		"answer": "shop",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "disaster",
		"answer": "catastrophe",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "verify",
		"answer": "confirm",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "silent",
		"answer": "soundless",
		"otherAnswers": []
	},
	{
		"question": "alert",
		"answer": "aware",
		"otherAnswers": []
	}
]
